这周末你想不想
Hey, want to spend some time
一起玩星球大战的新游戏
playing the new Star Wars game this weekend?
我说不准
Oh, I don't know.
我答应过自己要远离电脑
I kind of promised myself I'd get off the computer,
多点锻炼身体  多做些运动...
be more physically active. Get some exercise...
你马上要爬三层楼梯了
You're about to walk up three flights of stairs.
说得好  算我一个
Good point, I'm in.
我有个更好的主意
You know what would be great?
咱们像以前那样玩一把
Let's do it like the old days.
你是说游戏马拉松吗
You mean, are you talking gaming marathon?
没错  从周六早上开始
Yeah. Start Saturday morning,
连玩四十八个小时
go 48 hours,
带上睡袋  垃圾食品
sleeping bags, junk food...
关掉手机  避免老妈骚扰
Turn off our phones so our moms can't call.
就像几年前咱们玩魔兽世界那样
It would be like our World Of Warcraft a few years ago
最后邻居都报警了
when the neighbors called the cops on us.
他们打电话报警是因为受不了恶臭
They called the cops because of the smell.
人家还以为咱们死翘翘了呢
They thought we were dead.
那时的我们真是坏小子呀
We were badass back in the day.
好吧  就这么定了
All right, let's do it.
《星球大战：旧共和国》游戏背景设定在共和国军对抗帝国军的奥德兰内战时期
星球大战  四十八小时不停战
48 hours of Star Wars gaming.
在电影中奥德兰星球被帝国的超级兵器死星炸成碎片
开战吧  就像在奥德兰战区那样
It's on like Alderaan.
谢尔顿  取消你周末的行程
Hey, Sheldon, clear your weekend.
星球大战马拉松  周六上午正式开始
Starting Saturday morning, Star Wars marathon.
是看电影还是打电动
Movies or video games?
不  是桌游吗
No, board game?
还是集换式卡牌游戏
Or trading card games?
或是乐高  或是角色扮演
Or Lego's? Or dress up?
又或是看漫画书
Or comic books?!
难道是绘声绘色地朗读电影小说吗
Or dramatic readings of Novelizations?!
我都参加
Yes to all!
我们准备玩网游
We are going to play the online game.
网游
The online game?!
更妙
Bully!
先生们  虽然谢尔顿肯定非常喜欢
Gentlemen, as much as I'm sure Sheldon would enjoy
跟你们一起玩星际间的虚拟游戏
playing intergalactic make-believe,
但我们俩已经另有安排了
he and I have other plans.
我们要去参加弗罗拉姨妈的九十三岁生日派对
We are attending my Aunt Flora's 93rd birthday party.
你就跟她说我有事去不了了嘛
Just tell her I can't come.
如果我们不去  她会很失望的
She'll be disappointed if we don't show up.
她都九十三岁了
She's 93.
也失望不了几年了
She won't be disappointed for very long.
不  你等会  我可是遵守了
No, hang on. I followed all the protocols
恋爱协议里你制定的所有规定
set forth by you in the relationship agreement.
我提前七十二个小时提交了书面申请
I made a written record request 72 hours in advance.
我检查了车的胎压
I checked the tire pressure on the car.
我甚至还联系了疾病控制中心  问他们
I even contacted the Centers For Disease Control to find out
去橘子郡旅游要打什么疫苗
what shots they recommend for travel to Orange County.
顺便说一声  什么疫苗都不用打
FYI, it's none.
艾米  恋爱协议制订的初衷可不是为了
Amy, the relationship agreement was not designed
给咱俩任何一方行方便
for either one of us to get our way.
你就拿它来给自己行方便了呀
You use it to get your way.
我是拿它来做该做的事
I use it to get the right way.
事实证明  该做的事就是给我自己行方便
The fact that the right way is also my way
这真是个美妙的巧合
is a happy coincidence.
你都答应我了
You gave me your word.
你就要跟我去
You're coming with me.
我们会想你的  谢尔顿
We'll miss you, Sheldon.
好吧
Yeah, well,
谁会想把整个周末浪费
who wants to spend the whole weekend,
在一堆假想星球上跑来跑去
running around a bunch of pretend planets
跟不存在的怪兽打来打去呀
battling made up monsters.
小孩才这样呢
That's for babies.
话是没错  可这游戏有光剑呢
Yeah, but it's got lightsabers.
求求你了  艾米  这个游戏有光剑呢
Yeah, please, Amy! It's got lightsabers!
生活大爆炸第五季第十九集
你好  斯图尔特
Hello, Stewart.
你好  谢尔顿
Hey, Sheldon.
有什么需要帮忙的吗
Help you with anything?
有  我这周末要去参加一个
Yes, I'm attending a party this weekend
九十三岁老太太的生日派对
for a 93-year-old woman.
你能推荐份礼物吗
Can you recommend a gift?
我也不知道
Uh, I don't know.
在亚瑟王神剑的末端弄个网球
Could put a tennis ball on the end of Excalibur.
一根酷到爆的拐杖就诞生了
Make a pretty badass cane.
-那你这卖网球吗  -不卖
- Do you supply the tennis ball?  - No.
那算了
Then no.
还有什么
What else?
珍藏版的蝙蝠侠多功能腰带
Oh, have this collectors edition batman utility belt.
也许她可以把这个系在身上当药罐
Maybe she can use it as a wearable pill caddy.
她要是不穿一整套的话
Well, she'd just look silly wearing that
光系腰带会显得很傻
without the rest of the costume.
抱歉  谢尔顿  没了  我江郎才尽了
I'm sorry Sheldon, that's it. That's all I got.
这不是你的错
Oh, it's not your fault.
我已经去过模型火车店
I've been to the model train store.
无线电商店
I've been to Radio Shack.
这老太太的礼物可真难买
This woman is impossible to shop for.
要不是谢尔顿搞得到女人太让我震惊
I'd make fun of Sheldon for having girl problems
我早就开始取笑他连女人都搞不定了
if I wasn't in shock that Sheldon has girl problems.
没事  莱纳德  你尽管取笑我吧
No, Leonard, go ahead and mock.
就像我父亲常说的
Like my daddy always said,
"谢利  唯女子与小人难养也"
"Shelly, women aren't anything but flippin' pains in the bottom."
你父亲是这么说话的吗
That's what your father used to say?
我自动把脏话和语助词去掉
Well, I took out the bad words and the yeehaw,
但大意不变
but you get the gist.
如果你不想去参加派对的话  就别去
Look, if you don't want to go to the party, just don't go.
你是个成年人
You're a grown man.
就得有成年人的样子
Act like one.
跟艾米说  你想这周末不回家
Tell Amy you want to spend the weekend having a sleepover
跟你的朋友们一起玩游戏
and playing video games with your friends.
没准她还会喜欢你这样呢
Maybe she'll dig it.
女人就喜欢立场坚定的男人[直译为坚定的掌舵手]
Women like a firm hand on the tiller.
我连舵[阴蒂]在哪都找不到
I can never find the tiller.
我还有本教学书呢  还是于事无补
I got a book; it didn't help.
是啊  我以前总是想如果朝一日我沦为奴隶
Yeah, I always thought if I were ever enslaved,
那肯定是被另一个星球的高级物种奴役
it would be by an advanced species from another planet,
而不是某个来自格兰岱尔市的小妞
not some hotsy-totsy from Glendale.
我下载了一个应用程序
Now, I downloaded an app that
没准对现在的情况会有帮助哦
might be helpful in this situation.
你说得没错
You're right.
我这么聪明
I'm smart as a whip.
whip一词多义  有鞭子和聪明的意思
肯定能找到解决办法的
I should be able to figure this out.
话说我这周末
Hey, listen, I kind of made plans
打算跟他们几个玩  不过后来我想
with the guys this weekend, but then I wondered,
我们正处在恋爱测试阶段
because we're in this relationship-beta-test,
我是不是应该先问问你的意见
if I should have asked you first.
接着我又想  如果我真的先问你
Then I thought if I did check with you first,
你又可能觉得我对这段感情太认真了
then you'd think that I was taking things to seriously.
再后来  我就流鼻血了
And then-en I got a nosebleed.
你不用事事都先问我
You don't have to check with me.
你想干什么就干什么
Do whatever you want.
这不是我期待的反应  不过没关系
I guess I was hoping for a different reaction, but okay.
是吗  那你期待的是什么反应
Really, what were you hoping for?
我也不知道
I don't know,
或许你会小小地生气一下
maybe that you'd be a little upset,
然后意识到
and then you'd realize that
我是一匹向往自由的骏马
I'm a stallion that has to run free.
这点会让你小小地性奋一下
And that would turn you on a little.
行  我是个演员  再问我一遍
Okay, I'm an actress. Ask me again.
你介意我这个周末
Do you mind if I spend the weekend
跟他们几个玩网游吗
playing video games with the guys?
什么  整个周末
Wha... the entire weekend?
那我岂不是见不到你了
You mean I wouldn't see you at all?
可我...
But I j...
算了
No, no...
当初爱上你时我就知道了
I knew what I was getting into.
莱纳德这匹骏马是拴不住的
You can't put a saddle on Leonard Hofstadter.
哎哟  屋子里好像变热了
Oh, my, is it getting hot in here?
源于西班牙语  用于调情
是么  宝贝
Ay, papi.
Ay, papi?
这是什么呀
What is that?
演技大发挥
An acting choice.
这么说每次你性奋的时候
So you chose that when you become turned on,
墨西哥动画片《飞毛腿冈萨雷斯》
你就会变成飞毛鼠咯
you turn into Speedy Gonzalez?
你有意见吗  宝贝
Choo got a problem with that, papi?
佩妮  佩妮  佩妮
Penny! Penny! Penny!
不好意思  骏马
Sorry, Stallion.
你的长颈鹿疯友来了
Your weird friend Giraffe is here.
你好  佩妮
Hello, Penny!
我是过来送你礼物的
I just stopped by to bring you this gift.
小熊软糖  谢谢
Gummy bears? Thank you.
拿人家的手软  吃人家的嘴短
Now that you're in my debt...
麻烦你在艾米耳边吹吹风
...please manipulate Amy into releasing me
别让我去参加她姨妈的无聊生日派对
from my commitment to attend her aunt's tedious birthday party.
不可能
Not a chance.
好吧
All right.
我早料到软糖可能使不动你
I thought the candy might not be enough
那我提高价码吧
so let me up the ante.
这有几张库珀礼券
These are Cooper Coupons.
可以让我为你做各种事
These are for various things I can do for you.
比如这张
Um, oh, this one
可提供一次免费的语法检查
is for one free grammar check.
我可以帮你检查电邮  信件
You could use it for emails, letters,
纹身等等  诸如此类的东西
tattoos, what have you.
这张可有趣了
Oh, this is fun one!
用这张可以跟我在加州科学中心共度下午
This is an afternoon with me at the California Science Center,
我会现场指出他们的错误
where I point out their mistakes.
注意一下使用期限
Keep an eye on those expiration dates,
我就被骗过不止一次
I've been burned more than once.
够了  亲爱的  我绝对不会
All right, sweetie, I'm not going to get involved
干预你们的恋情
in your relationship.
拜托  不就是帮个忙嘛
Oh, come on. It's just a simple favor.
我上一次叫你帮我做事
Now, when's the last time I asked you
是什么时候
to do something for me?
昨天  你要我帮你看看
Yesterday. You made me look in your ear
你耳朵里是不是有瓢虫
to see if there was a ladybug in it.
我上一次叫你帮我做非紧急医疗的事
When is the last time I asked you to do something
是什么时候
that wasn't a medical emergency?
昨天  你要我帮你看看
Yesterday. You made me look in your ear
你耳朵里是不是有瓢虫
to see if there was a ladybug in it.
好吧  我别无选择
All right, then, I have no choice
只有执行B计划了
but to go on to plan B.
什么B计划
What's that?
我准备湿着头
I'm going to run around outside
去外面跑一圈  看看能不能感冒
with a wet head and try to catch a cold.
早上好
Good morning.
Hello.
我觉得你今天会玩得很开心的
I think you're really going to enjoy yourself today.
你不但能见到我的亲戚
Not only do you get to meet my relatives,
而且因为我姨妈的派对是疗养院承办的
but since my aunt's nursing home is catering the party,
所以所有的食品都软绵绵的
all of the food is incredibly soft.
就像给你的牙齿放假一样
It's like a vacation for your teeth.
好的
All right.
你确定你想去吗
You sure you're okay with this?
确定
Yes.
我决定找一个
I decided to find a way
即能出席派对又能玩得开心的方法
that I could have this experience and enjoy it.
谢谢  这对我来说意义重大
Thank you. That means a lot to me.
不用谢我
Oh, don't thank me.
要谢就谢无线技术
Thank wireless technology.
我发现即使出席你姨妈的无聊派对
I realized, I can go to your aunt's awful party
也一样能跟朋友们玩网游一整天
and still spend the whole day gaming with my friends.
谢尔顿  我的亲戚都想跟你聊聊
Sheldon, my relatives are going to want to talk to you,
而你却打算坐在一旁玩游戏吗
and you're going to be sitting there playing a game?
这未免太无礼了吧
Isn't that a little rude?
你放心  我有办法
Oh, I got that covered.
耳麦
Headset.
那些老家伙在说什么  我一个字都听不到
I won't hear a word the old geezers are saying.
既然你觉得玩游戏比
You know, if playing that game is more important to you
履行你对我的承诺还重要
than honoring your commitment to me,
你也不介意我告诉大家我要带男友出席
and you don't mind me showing up at a party all by myself
结果却孤家寡人现身在派对上的话
after I've already told everybody I'll be bringing somebody,
那我没话说
then, fine.
你回家去玩游戏吧
Go home and play your game.
谢谢
Thanks.
对了
Ooh, listen,
我不介意你带一块生日蛋糕给我
I wouldn't mind a piece of birthday cake,
前提是老家伙吹蜡烛时口水没飙出来
provided the old gal's candle blow is clean and dry.
东西齐了
Here you go.
我买了游戏期间我们需要的所有东西
I've got everything we'll need for the big game:
低脂火鸡肉干
low-fat turkey jerky...
低碳水化合物啤酒
low-carb beer...
只有一百卡路里的零食
100-calorie snack pack...
你买东西的时候   有顺便买条Y染色体吗
You pick up a Y chromosome while you were there?
男性染色体为XY  女人染性体为XX
缺乏Y染色体可能导致发育为娘娘腔
你也可能是没有Y染色体吧
You might be short one.
我是要在游戏里升级
Hey, I plan on leveling up in the game,
不是要升级我的泳衣尺码  真谢谢你了
not my swimsuit size, thank you very much.
先生们  游戏给我们提供了选择
Gentlemen, the game offers us a choice,
是选正义使者银河共和国呢
between playing for the Republic and the light side,
还是选大反派西斯帝国呢
or the Sith Empire and the dark side.
我们向来选做正义使者
Well, we're always the good guys.
在《龙与地下城》  咱是善良守法
In D&D, we're lawful good,
在《英雄之城》里  我们是英雄
in City Of Heroes, we're the heroes,
在《侠盗猎车手》
and Grand Theft Auto,
我们完事后立马付钱给妓女
we pay the prostitutes promptly,
还从不用球棒打她们
and never hit them with a bat.
是妓女啊
Those women are prostitutes?
你说她们是在为干细胞研究募资
You said they were raising money for stem cell research.
伙计们  我有惊喜要给大家哦
Hey, guys, I got a surprise.
如果是帮助女性肠胃运动的酸奶
Hm, if it's yogurt that helps ladies poop,
我觉得拉杰已经捷足先登了
I think Raj beat you to it.
不是  伯纳黛特要跟我们一起玩
No. Bernadette's going to be playing with us.
很不错吧  对吧  那是当然
So, that's pretty cool, huh? Right? Sure it is, yeah.
什么  你邀请了你的女友
What, you invited your girlfriend?!
这可是我们的男生周末
This is supposed to be our weekend!
我也没办法  昨晚她说
I had no choice. Last night, she said,
我们明天一起吃早午餐吧
"Why don't we go out for brunch tomorrow
然后再去植物园
and then maybe the Arboretum."
我说  不行
And I said, "Well, no,
我答应他们几个
I promised the guys I was going to
周末一起玩游戏的
play a video game with them all weekend."
然后她说  听起来挺好玩的
And she said, "That sounds like fun.
我能加入吗
Can I come, too?"
我沉默了一会儿  然后她说
And then I didn't answer for a second, and then she said,
你是不想让我一起吗
"Well, do you not want me to come?"
然后我就给她买了个新笔记本和一套游戏
And then I bought her a new laptop and the game,
然后她现在正在停车呢
and she's parking the car right now.
鞭子抽男人的程序
Is the whip sound app
符合此情此景吗
contextually appropriate here?
可以  但我觉得你等得有点久
Uh, it is, but I think you might've waited too long
笑点都过去了
for it to be funny.
我说错了  还是很搞笑
I was wrong; it's still funny.
太好了
Oh, good.
艾米  怎么了
Amy, what's wrong?
我男友是个混球
My boyfriend's a jerk.
好吧  他肯定不是劈腿
Well, I know he didn't cheat on you,
那是什么事
so what happened?
我孤家寡人参加我姨妈的派对
I had to go to my aunt's party all by myself,
人人都嘲弄我说
and everybody was like,
"你那个总挂在嘴边的男朋友呢"
"Where's this boyfriend you're always talking about?
"是真有其人  还是你编出来的呀"
"Is he real, or did you make him up like Armen,
比如之前那个小马农阿曼"
the miniature horse breeder?"
谁是小马农阿曼
Who's Armen the miniature horse breeder?
是我为了摆脱家人唠叨  而捏造出来的男友
The pretend boyfriend I invented to get my family off my back.
但很快就被揭穿了  因为我答不上来
It unraveled quickly when I couldn't answer the question
"你俩怎么认识的"
"How'd you two meet?"
要是我  我会说是在一场小马秀上
I would have thought at a miniature horse show.
这答案不错
Oh, that's good.
我慌了神  便说是在伍德斯托克音乐节
I panicked and said Woodstock.
我只是想在我家人面前炫耀一下谢尔顿
I just wanted to show Sheldon off to my family.
当然啦  我懂的
Sure, I get that.
他是你的初恋男友嘛
I mean, he's your first boyfriend and all.
他不仅是我初恋男友  还是最好的男友
Not just my first boyfriend, he's the best boyfriend.
你想想
I mean, think about it.
我在跟谢尔顿·库珀交往哎
I'm dating Sheldon Cooper.
没错
Yes.
还别有用心
On purpose.
他帅气十足  身材修长
He's handsome, he's lanky,
才华横溢
he's brilliant,
而且他的皮肤苍白无血色
and his skin has that pale, waxy quality.
吸血鬼式的病态肤色的确是新性感指标
Well, sickly is the new sexy.
没错
Yeah.
艾米
You know, Amy,
有时候  当你跟你真正喜欢的人
sometimes when you're in a relationship with someone
谈恋爱时  不好的地方是
you really care about, the sucky part is,
会让你更容易受伤
it leaves you open to getting hurt.
你担心过莱纳德这么对你吗
Do you ever worry about Leonard doing that to you?
问得真搞笑  从来没有
That's hilarious. No.
干掉他  干掉他
Get that guy! Get that guy!
罗斯坦考夫斯基博士
Dr. Rostenkowski,
要知道
it may interest you to know
你这样瞎喊还不如
that saying "Pew, pew, pew" isn't as effective
直接按爆炸键有效
as pressing your blaster key.
同样  再怎么乱叫
In the same way that saying "Whee!"
陆行艇也不会跑起来
doesn't make the land speeder go.
拉杰  帝国军队接近你了
Raj, Imperial Troopers on your tail.
搞定了
Got him.
当甘地提倡他的非暴力理论时
When Gandhi advocated his philosophy of non-violence,
他肯定不明白打打杀杀有多痛快
I bet he didn't know how much fun it was killing stuff.
好了  我们把他们全杀光了
All right, I think we got them all.
分战利品吧
Let's divide up the loot.
看我拿到的这件漂亮的紫色长袍
Ooh, look at this pretty purple robe I just got.
你也该穿上你的  咱俩多搭呀
You should put on yours and then we'll match.
我费了好大劲才得到这身盔甲
But I worked hard to get this armor.
抱歉  我只是觉得
Sorry, I just thought it'd be nice
让别人看出咱俩是一对很有爱
if people knew we were a couple.
好吧  我换
Fine, I'll change.
-我不想玩游戏  -拜托
- I don't think I want to play a game. - Oh, come on!
他们在对门玩得不亦乐乎  咱也该玩玩
They're playing one across the hall-- we should, too.
好了  我们轮流往桌子上扔硬币
Okay, we are gonna take turns bouncing a quarter
如果谁把它弹到这个杯子里
off the table, and if it goes into this cup,
另一个人就得喝一杯
the other person has to drink.
然后你再继续
Then you get to go again...
像这样吗
Like that?
没错  新手运气好而已
Wow. Yeah, b-beginner's luck.
现在呢  我把这一整杯啤酒喝掉
So, now I will drink this entire cup of beer,
然后你再继续
and you will go again...
好吧
All right.
现在我就喝光这杯酒
So, yeah, okay, now I'm gonna drink this entire cup
然后再喝掉一杯
and then I'm going to drink another one.
行了  说真的  住手  搞毛啊
Okay, seriously, stop. What the hell?
我小时候经常
Spent a lot of my childhood
往许愿池扔硬币  希望能有朋友
throwing coins into wishing wells hoping for friends.
到了某种程度  你就会开始玩花样
At a certain point, you start doing trick shots
好让这游戏不那么枯燥
just to keep things interesting.
等我喝完再投  等等
Whoa, give me a second to catch up here. Hold on.
那是我男朋友的声音
That'd be my boyfriend
宁愿和朋友玩无趣的星际迷航游戏
happier playing his dopey Star Trek game with his friends
也不愿跟我一起出去
than hanging out with me.
-是大战  -什么
- Wars. - What?
是星际大战
Star Wars.
把这俩搞错的话  他们会大发雷霆的
They get all cranky when you mix the two up.
有什么区别吗
What's the difference?
绝对没区别
There's absolutely no difference.
怎样才能让他对我更好呢
How do I get him to treat me better?
好吧
All right.
我来给你上上女友基础课程吧
Let me give you a little girlfriend 101.
通常使出的第一招
Usually the first move out of the gate
不跟他滚床单
is you withhold sex,
但这招得等谢尔顿到青春期后才有用
but that will work better after Sheldon hits puberty.
所以  我认为
So, I'd say...
对他采取不予理睬政策
give him the silent treatment.
不行  他爱死这样了
No, he loves that.
我们俩共处一个房间
Our record for sitting in a room together
但互相不讲话的记录是六个半小时
and not speaking to each other is six-and-a half hours.
他还说那晚他过得很开心
He said it was a magical evening.
好吧  那我们就只能采取
All right, then we're gonna have to go
最古老也最有效的那招了
with an oldie but goodie;
大吵大闹
making a scene.
这个我可不大擅长
I don't think I'd be good at that.
所以说有我这闺蜜你幸运死了
That's why you're lucky to have me.
在我家乡奥马哈  有餐厅不允许我进去
Back in Omaha, there are two different restaurants
就是红辣椒饭店  我还被黑名单了两次
I'm not allowed into. Both Chili's.
伯纳黛特  记住你是我们团的补血师
Bernadette, remember, your character's the healer in our group.
你不能只给霍华德回血  要给大家回啊
You're in charge of healing all of us, not just Howard.
我情不自禁嘛
I can't help it.
我的华仔小巫师受伤了呢
My Howie Wowie has an owie.
这真是我所听过的
That is the most sickeningly sweet thing
最恶心的甜言蜜语
I have ever experienced.
我正用"蜡烛糖"吸"酷A果汁"呢
And I am sipping Kool-Aid through a Red Vine.
谢尔顿·库珀  我有帐要跟你算
Sheldon Cooper, I've got a bone to pick with you,
我要当着你所有朋友的面算这笔帐
and I'm about to do it in front of all your friends.
没错  跟他好好算账  算得他裤衩都保不住
Yeah, you pick that bone. You pick that bone clean!
我要当众羞辱你
I'm gonna publicly shame you,
然后我就坐等社会的压力
and then sit back as societal pressure
迫使你修正自己的行为
compels you to modify your behavior.
迎头痛击啊
Ooh, buuurn!
如果你以后还不对我好一点
And if you don't start treating me better,
我就跟你分手
I'm leaving you
然后跟小马农阿曼一起
for a miniature horse breeder named Armen.
哪个阿曼
Armen who?
阿文就是...见鬼
Armen... damn it.
谢尔顿  她想在家人面前炫耀一下你
Look, Sheldon, she wanted to show you off to her family,
你却放她鸽子  好吧
and you stood her up, okay?
看看她这可爱又伤感的表情
Look at this adorable, smushy face.
多伤感  多痛苦  多郁闷啊
Smush, smush, smush.
你弄痛我了
You're hurting me.
错  弄痛你的是谢尔顿
No, Sheldon hurt you.
之前他让我心痛  现在是你让我脸痛
Before; now it's you.
我明白了
I think I understand.
这世界上只有你一个
You're the one person
可以说谢尔顿·库珀是你男友
who can say Sheldon Cooper is your boyfriend,
但这话毕竟有些空洞
but that rings hollow
如果你不能让他亲自去证明
if you can't lord him over others in the flesh.
我忘了  我能让他们蓬荜生辉
I forget what I bring to the party
我走后  也会让他们怅然若失
and what I take away when I leave.
请接受这些珍贵的库珀优惠券
Please accept these valuable Cooper Coupons...
就当补偿你吧
...as restitution.
谢尔顿  她才不要你这些傻不拉唧的...
Sheldon, she doesn't want your stupid...
科学中心  现在使用
Ooh, Science Center. Redeeming.
出发吧
Let's go.
干得好  艾米·菲拉·福勒
Well played, Amy Farrah Fowler.
等我穿件外套
Let me get my coat.
长大点吧  莱纳德
Oh, grow up, Leonard.
各位打断一下
But e-excuse me,
我有话要说
I have something to say.
你们可能都没意识到
None of you may realize it,
但我真的很期待这个周末
but I was very much looking forward to this weekend.
就像回到了从前
It was gonna be like the old days--
在你们几个各自有女朋友之前
the four of us hanging out playing video games
我们四个聚在一起玩游戏
before you guys all got girlfriends.
你们到底知不知道
Do you have any idea what it's like
只有我一个人没女朋友  是什么心情呀
to be the only one without a girlfriend?
即使我哪天有了女友
Even if I get one someday,
我仍是最后一名  比谢尔顿还晚泡到妞
I'll still be the guy who got a girl after Sheldon Cooper!
看  女人就是这么大吵大闹的
And that's how a girl makes a scene.
抱歉  亲爱的
I'm sorry, sweetie.
你说得对  你该好好度周末
You're right. You deserve your weekend.
来吧艾米  我们走
Come on, Amy, let's go.
那科学中心什么时候能去啊
What about the Science Center?
我喝高呕吐的时候  让你搂着我头发
I'll let you hold my hair while I throw up.
改天再去吧
Rain check.
我也该走了
I'm gonna go, too.
-我会想你的  -我才想你呢
- I'll miss you. - I'll miss you.
-我更想你  -我才更想...
- I'll miss you more. - No, I'll...
快走吧
Just leave!
好了
Okay, now.
本来就应该这样
This is the way it's supposed to be.
男人齐聚  共同杀敌
Men together, fighting the forces of evil.
说得对
Hear! Hear!
真不敢相信这一瓶只有64大卡
I can't believe this is only 64 calories.
霍华德·乔尔·沃罗威茨
Howard Joel Wolowitz!
我整整担心了你两天
I've been worried sick for two days,
我知道你把手机关了
and I know you turned off your phone!
马上给我开门
You open up this door right now
老娘都走到这来找你了
because I've had it up to here!
停尸房和医院我都找了一圈
I have been to the morgue and the hospital,
这该死的楼梯
and I spent the last half hour
让我爬了半个小时
walking up these ferkakta stairs!
老娘在召唤  我该走了
That's my ride; got to go.